<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    studente: Lorenzo Simoni
    matricola: 549507
    corso: codifica testi 2019-20

    Marcare un testo plain text di circa 3000 caratteri a
    piacere.

    Utilizzare puntatori, note, lista, glossario marcare nomi, rs,
    term.
-->
<!DOCTYPE TEI SYSTEM "tei_all.dtd">

<TEI>
    <teiHeader xml:lang="it">
        <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
                <title>Fate/Requiem: versione elettronica</title>
                <respStmt>
                    <resp>Conversione TEI P5 a cura di</resp>
                    <name>L. Simoni</name>
                </respStmt>
            </titleStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
                <publisher>Università di Pisa</publisher>
                <date>2020-05-02</date>
            </publicationStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
                <bibl>
                    <title>Fate/Requiem</title>
                    <author>Meteor Hoshizora</author>
                    <publisher><ref target="http://typemoon.com/book/">TYPE-MOON BOOKS</ref></publisher>
                    <date>2018-12-31</date>
                </bibl>
            </sourceDesc>
        </fileDesc>
    </teiHeader>

    <text xml:lang="en">

        <front>
            <titlePage>
                <docAuthor>Meteor Hoshizora</docAuthor>
                <docTitle>
                <titlePart type="main">Fate/Requiem</titlePart>
                </docTitle>
                <docEdition>1st edition</docEdition>
                <graphic url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxytlP-P8QJBv31qcqk44m_12lpsUO7sG5OzXknexQlJzxVirpkyb3_36WKF6J8AYKW5DySFkkDIOQXDl9drt6NhuRKljE24uekjmI2Z1vkpyh8EKGpKaIIjCpnX3M" />
                <docImprint>
                    <pubPlace>JAPAN</pubPlace>
                    <publisher><ref target="http://typemoon.com/book/">TYPE-MOON BOOKS</ref></publisher>
                    <date>2018-12-31</date>
                </docImprint>
            </titlePage>
        </front>
        
        <body>
            

            <head>Prologue</head>

            <div n="1">
                <p>People have taken to calling me <emph rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">the Reaper</emph>. Only once have I ever been thanked for my work.</p>

                <p>This was awful. This had to have been one of the worst nights of my life.</p>

                <p> My pursuers had grown in number once again. They were dividing, at an incredible rate. 
                    Monsters who lived only to separate humans by component parts; no matter how many I cut down, I couldn’t stem the tide.
                </p>

                <p>The effects of the Body Augmentations I’d equipped to my own body had long faded. The fetish charms
                    of
                    which
                    I’d prepared so many, into which I’d stockpiled so much mana, had all been expended. My heightened
                    eyesight, my
                    improved cardiopulmonary functions and all the rest were now ragged and exhausted, barely at the
                    level
                    of an
                    ordinary human. All that I had left to rely on now was my own flesh and bone, my own blood and guts:
                    the
                    body that I’d somehow managed to keep intact for these fourteen years.</p>

                <p>That, and the lessons that had been carved into my heart by a needle of regret.</p>

                <p>The Material Barrier that coated every inch of my skin had dwindled to its base parameters. A single
                    solid
                    hit would be enough to blow me to pieces, like a plate dropped on the floor. But I had a strange
                    premonition
                    that all this was only a prelude to what was waiting for me; to what would really make this the
                    worst
                    night of my
                    life.</p>

                <p>I sprinted through alleyways, drenched in muddy water, covered in unreclaimed garbage. Once,
                    worshippers
                    would take this road to reach Kanda Shrine. I tumbled down one of the narrow, steep sets of stone
                    stairs
                    that
                    split off into innumerable branches. As I did so, I landed a flying kick on the behinds of the two
                    men ahead of me.
                    The uninvited guests.</p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">Ugh, we still not at the harbour? My heart’s about to damn well burst,
                        girl! I’m gonna drop dead right
                        here!</q></p>

                <p>One of the men tilted his neck to look at me.</p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">You know damn well you aren’t! If you’re gonna live as long as you
                        have, you should try to have the
                        courtesy to scrape together a century or two’s worth of wisdom! Or if you can’t do that, at
                        least
                        just shut up and run!</q></p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">Hey now, hey now! If I’m ever gonna put a sock in it, it’ll be when I
                        go meet the Buddha! You could
                        cut my
                        head off right now and my mouth would still be chatterin’!</q></p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">Like hell it would, because I’d tie it shut myself! With a good metre
                        or two of wire!</q></p>

                <p>How many dozens of times had he made some dumb immortality gag? It had gone beyond getting on my
                    nerves.
                    He
                    knew better than anyone that he could be carved to pieces or shot full of holes, and it still
                    wouldn’t
                    be enough
                    to kill him. Although, for all that, he was in almost as sorry a state as I was right now.</p>

                <p>Even in this day and age, when immortality was hardly a rarity, he was still making me listen to his
                    nonsense. And what was he doing talking about meeting the Buddha anyway, when he was a Jew?</p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">Just shut up and keep moving!</q></p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">…Understood.</q> The other man nodded. His partner skidded as he
                    rounded a corner, almost toppling,
                    and he
                    reached out to grab his belt, righting him as naturally as if he were taking hold of a jib sheet.
                </p>

                <p><q>Once we reach the docks, they cannot best us.</q></p>

                <p>His wild black hair and unshaven beard carried the smell of the deep. It was something wholly unlike
                    this
                    town’s artificial landscapes: the scent of real sea breezes and real shafts of sunlight, carved deep
                    into his soul.</p>

                <p><q rend="PRE lsquo POST rsquo">Understood. I’m counting on you, Captain.</q></p>

                <p>His response was silence.</p>

                <p>The starkness of the difference between himself and his companion still took me aback. Could it be
                    that
                    sailors simply disliked wasting words? I didn’t think so. He likely just didn’t trust me yet. In any
                    case, though, I
                    was glad that I had not made an enemy of this strong, silent man of the sea. Things could have
                    easily
                    have gone
                    differently.</p>
            
                <p>And besides, I couldn’t deny that I had found something unexpectedly endearing in the twin grey
                    flames
                    burning beneath his chiselled brow.</p>
            </div>
            <div n="2">
                <p>Needless to say, the captain’s dominion was the sea; on land, he could not fully exercise his power. That was why we were now making haste to the harbour.</p>

                <p>I was only collateral damage to the monsters pursuing us. Their real target was my companions: the two men whose protection constituted my current job. One was a Heroic Spirit, who had come in answer to a summons: a <term xml:id="SVN">Servant</term>. The zenith of necromantic magic (<gloss target="#SVN">Servants are spirits made into special familiars of the highest rank, referred to as Ghost Liners by the Mage's Association, that are bound to the Master. Typically Heroic Spirits under most systems, they can also sometimes be Divine Spirits, Phantoms, Wraiths, and living people depending on various circumstances. Pure Heroic Spirits, the "main body" in the Throne of Heroes, can only be summoned by the World, and summoning even one is considered to be a miraculous occurrence. Read more here <ptr target="https://typemoon.fandom.com/wiki/Servant"/></gloss>). The other was human; <emph rend="italic">was</emph> human, for he had abandoned his humanity a long time ago.</p>
                    
                <p>Any denizen of this city would have told you that Servants are safe and harmless; but peaceful and happy though this thought may be, only they believed it. That was why people like me existed: to maintain the illusions of their everyday, by doing the work that anyone else would revile. The work of killing Servants with our own two hands.</p>
            </div>
        </body>
    </text>
</TEI>